A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, Administration, Program and Policy, RG 3 FA112
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Administration, Program and Policy, 2
  - General Program and Policy, 1913-1991; 900; 99 document cases
    - Organization - Anniversary - Reports and Supplementary Material - Org Ann-1 - Org Ann-5e, 1963 (Box 25, Folder 137)
      Org Ann-5e: Acceptances, declinations to Anniversary celebration; Moruzzi, Bragg, Tinbergen; Letters of invitations and acceptances/declinations for visiting lectureships; Sample letter of invitation and list of similar letters sent to individuals with checklist, notification of acceptance/declination; April 2, 1963
    - Organization - Anniversary Dinner, 1962-1963 (Box 25, Folder 138)
    - Organization - Anniversary Dinner - Fellowship TV Program, 1962-1963 (Box 25, Folder 139)
    - Organization - Anniversary Dinner - Picture Book, 1962-1963 (Box 25, Folder 140)
    - Financial Administration and Corporate Responsibility (Box 025A, Folder 0140A)
    - Financial Administration and Corporate Responsibility (Box 025A, Folder 0140A)
    - Organization - Anniversary Dinner - Picture Book, 1964-1968 (Box 26, Folder 141)
    - Organization - Anniversary Dinner - Picture Book, 1964-1968 (Box 26, Folder 142)
    - Organization - Anniversary Dinner - Picture Book - List of Letters of Acknowledgment (Box 26, Folder 143)
    - Organization - Anniversary Dinner - Picture Book - Sample Collection of Letters in Acknowledgment (Box 26, Folder 144)
    - Program and Policy, 1949-1957 (Box 26, Folder 145)
    - Program and Policy, 1949-1957 (Box 26, Folder 146)
    - Program and Policy, 1958-November 1972 (Box 27, Folder 147)
    - Program and Policy, 1958-November 1972 (Box 27, Folder 148)
    - Program and Policy, 1958-November 1972 (Box 27, Folder 149)
    - Program and Policy, 1958-November 1972 (Box 27, Folder 150)
    - Program and Policy, 1958-November 1972 (Box 27, Folder 151)
    - Program and Policy, December 1972-1973 (Box 28, Folder 152)
    - Program and Policy, December 1972-1973 (Box 28, Folder 153)
    - Program and Policy, December 1972-1973 (Box 28, Folder 154)
    - Program and Policy - Reports - Pro-42, 42a, 43, 45a, 45A-X, 45b, 45c-g, 1930-1950 (Box 28, Folder 155)
      Pro-42: Alan Gregg; Appraisal of Successes and Failures of Foundations; March 26, 1949
      Pro-42a: Cheater I. Barnard; Reflections at the End of Year One; July 1, 1949
      Pro-43: Flora M. Rhind; Policy Regarding the Making of Grants for Buildings; November 10, 1950
      Pro-45a: Financial Administration; April 16, 1930
      Pro-45A-X: Collection of Program, Policy, and Organization Documents (includes list of Documents); 1952
      Pro-45b: The Report on the Committee on Appraisal and Plan (copy filed 900 Pro-27); December 11, 1934
      Pro-45c-g: Report of Special Committee (with corrections adopted) "to consider questions relating to the organization, operation, and procedure of the Foundation" (Copies 1-3 filed 900 Org-32. Copy of 45g filed 900 Pro-41a); December 10, 1935
    - Program and Policy - Reports - Pro-45h,i,j, 1942-1949 (Box 29, Folder 156)
      Pro-45h: Program of the International Health Division, Statement Prepared for the Scientific Directors (copy filed 908 Pro-24)
      Pro-45i: Report of the Rockefeller Health Commission (Copy filed 700 RFHC Rep-3); July 1, 1946-December 31, 1947
      Pro-45j: Special Report to the Board of Scientific Directors of the International Health Division of the Rockefeller Foundation Human Ecology (population) (Copy filed 900 Pro Pop-1); November 4, 1949
    - Program and Policy - Reports - Pro-45m, r, s, t, u, x, 1939-1951 (Box 29, Folder 157)
      Pro-45m: Report of the Committee of Review, Appraisal and Advice,, The Rockefeller Foundation Division of Natural Sciences (copy filed 915 Pro-19); May 1939
      Pro-45r: Maston Bates; Human Ecology and the Rockefeller Foundation, Final Report to Cheater I. Barnard (Copy file 900 Pro Pop-2); October 22, 1951
      Pro-45s: Report to the Trustees' Committee on Humanities in American Institutions (Copy filed 911 Pro-16); February 15, 1943
      Pro-45t: Report of the Rockefeller Foundation in Humanities, History, Future Projections, Grants and Fellowships (Copy file 911 Pro-17)
      Pro-45u: Humanities - Summary of Current Operations (Copy filed 911 Pro-19); April 1, 1949
      Pro-45x: Organization of Data of the Rockefeller Foundation (Includes subsidiary boards and divisions) CMB, inc., PUMC, LSRM, Spelman Fund, GEB, IEB, RIMR); May 1950
    - Program and Policy - Reports - Pro-46, 47a,b, 1955-1963 (Box 29, Folder 158)
      Pro-46: Dean Rusk; Notes on the Rockefeller Foundation Program, Prepared for Discussion at Meeting of Board of Trustees 12/1-2/1953; December 1, 1953
      Pro-47: Dean Rusk; Notes on the Rockefeller Foundation Program (Revision of 900 Pro-46); March 22, 1955
      Pro-47a: Proposals for the Future Program of the Rockefeller Foundation; December 1, 1962
      Pro-47b: The Rockefeller Foundation Program Principles and Content; April3, 1963
    - Program and Policy - Reports - Pro-51-53, 1933-1968 (Box 29, Folder 159)
      Pro-51: John Marshall; Relations of the Foundation with Governmental and Intergovernmental Agencies; November 3, 1950
      Pro-52: Secretary's Notes on Discussion at Selected Trustee Meetings; 1933-1953
      Pro-53: The Rockefeller Foundation Five Year Review and Projection; December 1968
    - Program and Policy - Reports - Pro-54 - Pro-56, 1969-1970 (Box 30, Folder 160)
      Pro-54: Trustee Report; December 1969
      Pro-55: Trustee Report; April 1970
      Pro-56: Director's Statements on Program; April 1, 1970
    - Program and Policy - Reports - Pro-57 - Pro-60, 1970-1973 (Box 30, Folder 161)
      Pro-57: Trustee Report; May 1970
      Pro-58: Tustee Report; April 1971
      Pro-59: Interim Report, Trustee Program Review Committee; April 4, 1973
      Pro-60: Report on Organization and Administration, Presented to Trustee Programm Committee; May 18, 1973
    - Program and Policy - Reports - Pro-61, 1973 (Box 30, Folder 162)
      Pro-61: Second Iterim Report, Trustee Program Review Committee; September 19, 1973
    - Program and Policy - Reports - Pro-62, December 3, 1973 (Box 30, Folder 163)
      Pro-62: Final Report, Trustee Program Review Committee; December 3, 1973
    - Program and Policy - Reports - Pro-63, 64, 1973-1974 (Box 30, Folder 164)
      Pro-63: Foundation Executive Group; October 4, 1973
      Pro-64: The Course Ahead - The Rockefeller Foundation in the Next Five Years; May 29, 1974
    - Program and Policy - Area Studies, 1944, 1946-1951, 1954-1955, 1957, 1959, 1961 (Box 31, Folder 165)
    - Program and Policy - Area Studies - Reports - Pro Area-1 - Pro Area-2, 1950, 1954 (Box 31, Folder 166)
      Pro-Area-1: John Marshall; Area Studies in the Near East; June 27, 1950
      Pro-Area-2: Charles Burton Fahs; Widening Our Cultural Horizons; November 12, 1954
    - Program and Policy - Atomic Energy, 1945-1947, 1954-1957, 1959 (Box 31, Folder 167)
    - Program and Policy - Base Records, 1937-1941, 1949-1950, 1972-1973 (Box 31, Folder 168)
    - Program and Policy - Children, 1972, 1975-1977, 1980 (Box 31, Folder 169)
    - Program and Policy - Children, 1972, 1975-1977, 1980 (Box 31, Folder 170)
    - Program and Policy - Children - Supplementary Material (Box 32, Folder 171)
    - Program and Policy - Children - Supplementary Material (Box 32, Folder 172)
    - Program and Policy - Committee on Review, 1957-1959 (Box 32, Folder 173)
    - Program and Policy - Committee on Review - Supplementary Material, 1958 (Box 32, Folder 174)
    - Program and Policy - Environmental Science, 1965-1969 (Box 32, Folder 175)
    - Program and Policy - Environmental Science, 1970-1978, 1980 (Box 33, Folder 176)
    - Program and Policy - Environmental Science, 1970-1978, 1980 (Box 33, Folder 177)
    - Program and Policy - Environmental Science, 1970-1978, 1980 (Box 33, Folder 178)
    - Program and Policy - Environmental Science - Supplementary Material, 1969, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 179)
    - Program and Policy - Environmental Science - Reports - Pro Env-1, 1972 (Box 33, Folder 180)
      Pro Env-1: R. W. Richardson, Jr. Director; Quality of the Environment; July 1972
    - Program and Policy - Environmental Science - Reports - Pro Env-1a - Pro Env-8, 1970-1976 (Box 34, Folder 181)
      Pro Env-1a: Quality of the Environment; Director's Statements on Program; April 1970
      Pro-Env-2: Quality of the Environment Report, Presented to Trustee Program Committee; May 17, 1973
      Pro-Env-3: Quality of the Environment Program, Summary Statements, Presented to Trustee Program Committee; May 17, 1973
      Pro-Env-4: Quality of the Environmnet Program, Background Information, Presented to the Trustee Program Committee; May 17, 1973
      Pro-Env-5: Quality of the Environment Report, Report to the Trustees; April 1975
      Pro-Env-6: Quality of the Environment, Program Committee Meeting; September 9, 1976
      Pro-Env-7: A Special Report from the Rockefeller Foundation, Four Universities Achieving Environmental Quality through Environmental Education and Research; No Date
      Pro Env-8: Minutes of the Trustee/Staff Program Review Committee, Environmental Sciences; September 9, 1976
    - Program and Policy - Environmental Science - Committee Minutes, 1973-1977 (Box 34, Folder 182)
    - Program and Policy - Environmental Science - Committee Minutes, 1973-1977 (Box 34, Folder 183)
    - Program and Policy - Environmental Science - Consultants - Mann, Floyd, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 184)
    - Program and Policy - Environmental Science - Consultants, A-L, 1970-1980 (Box 34, Folder 185)
    - Program and Policy - Environmental Science - Consultants, M-Z, 1973-1981 (Box 35, Folder 186)
    - Program and Policy - Environmental Science - "Four Universities", 1972-1975 (Box 35, Folder 187)
    - Program and Policy - Environmental Science - "Four Universities", 1972-1975 (Box 35, Folder 188)
    - Program and Policy - Environmental Science - "Four Universities", 1972-1975 (Box 35, Folder 189)
    - Program and Policy - Environmental Science - "Four Universities", 1972-1975 (Box 35, Folder 190)
    - Program and Policy - Environmental Science - History, 1977-1981, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 191)
    - Program and Policy - Environmental Science - History - Reports - Pro Envh-1, no date (Box 36, Folder 192)
      Pro Envh-1: John Lear; Report on the Quality of the Environment Program, Chapters 1-17; no date
    - Program and Policy - Environmental Science - History - Reports - Pro Envh-2, 1973 (Box 36, Folder 193)
      Pro Envh-2: John Lear; Quality of the Environment Report (draft) - Chapters 18-28, Presented to Trustee Program Committee; May 17, 1973
    - Program and Policy - Environmental Science - Pesticide Conference, 1970, 1972-1975 (Box 36, Folder 194)
    - Program and Policy - Environmental Science - Pesticide Conference, 1970, 1972-1975 (Box 36, Folder 195)
    - Program and Policy - Environmental Science - Pesticide Conference - Supplementary Material (Box 37, Folder 196)
    - Program and Policy - Food, 1943-1944 (Box 37, Folder 197)
    - Program and Policy - Food, 1943-1944 (Box 37, Folder 198)
    - Program and Policy - Food, 1943-1944 (Box 37, Folder 199)
    - Program and Policy - Food, 1943-1944 (Box 37, Folder 200)
    - Program and Policy - Food, 1972-1976 (Box 38, Folder 201)
    - Program and Policy - Food, 1972-1976 (Box 38, Folder 202)
    - Program and Policy - Food, 1972-1976 (Box 38, Folder 203)
    - Program and Policy - Food, 1972-1976 (Box 38, Folder 204)
    - Program and Policy - Food, 1977-1982 (Box 39, Folder 205)
    - Program and Policy - Food, 1977-1982 (Box 39, Folder 206)
    - Program and Policy - Food - Reports - Pro Food-1, 1a, 2, 2a, 1943-1970 (Box 39, Folder 207)
      Pro-Food-1: Food as Possible Field of Interest for the Rockefeller Foundation; November 4, 1943
      Pro-Food-1a: Toward the Conquest of Hunger, Excerpt from Report to the Trustees; December 1963
      Pro-Food-2: Charles Glen King; Nutrition Program; August 17, 1964
      Pro-Food-2a: Conquest of Hunger, Director's Statements on Program; April 1970
    - Program and Policy - Food - Report - Pro Food-3, 1974 (Box 39, Folder 0207A)
      Pro-Food-3: Conquest of Hunger Program; December 1974
    - Program and Policy - Food - Reports - Pro Food-4,5, 1973, 1976 (Box 39, Folder 208)
      Pro-Food-4: Conquest of Hunger, Committee Minutes; January 1973
      Pro Food-5: Conquest of Hunger, Program Committee Meeting; October 14, 1976
    - Program and Policy - Food - Reports - Pro Food-6 - Pro Food-9, 1982 (Box 40, Folder 209)
      Pro-Food-6: The Rockefeller Foundation Conquest of Hunger Program, Report to the Trustees; September 13, 1982
      Pro Food-7: Conquest of Hunger Program, Report to the Trustees, Annex A, Backround on New Initiatives; September 13, 1982
      Pro Food-8: Conquest of Hunger Program, Report to the Trustees, Annex B, Background Infromation on Current Activities; September 13, 1982
      Pro-Food-9: Conquest of Hunger Program, Report to the Trustees, Annex C, Invited Papers By External Specialists; September 13, 1982
    - Program and Policy - Food - Reports - Pro Food-9a, 1982 (Box 40, Folder 210)
      Pro-Food-9a: Terms of Reference for Consultants Review of Conquest of Hunger Program (draft); January 22, 1982
    - Program and Policy - Food - Reports - Pro Food-9b, 1982 (Box 40, Folder 211)
      Pro-Food-9b: Workshop - Conquest of Hunger Program Review; May 21, 1982
    - Program and Policy - Food - Consultants - Bradfield, Robert B., 1971-1975 (Box 40, Folder 212)
    - Program and Policy - Food - Consultants - Harpstead, Dale D., 1972-1973 (Box 40, Folder 213)
    - Program and Policy - Food - Consultants - Scrimshaw, Nevin S., 1965-1966, 1968-1971 (Box 40, Folder 214)
    - Program and Policy - Food - Consultants - A-Z, 1973 (Box 40, Folder 215)
    - Program and Policy - Food - Review, 1981-March 1982 (Box 40, Folder 216)
    - Program and Policy - Food - Review, April-December 1982 (Box 41, Folder 217)
    - Program and Policy - Food - Review, April-December 1982 (Box 41, Folder 218)
    - Program and Policy - Food Policy, 1977-January 1979 (Box 41, Folder 219)
    - Program and Policy - Food Policy, 1977-January 1979 (Box 41, Folder 220)
    - Program and Policy - Food Policy, 1977-January 1979 (Box 41, Folder 221)
    - Program and Policy - Food Policy, February 1979-1981 (Box 42, Folder 222)
    - Program and Policy - Food Policy, February 1979-1981 (Box 42, Folder 223)
    - Program and Policy - Food Policy, February 1979-1981 (Box 42, Folder 224)
    - Program and Policy - Food Policy, February 1979-1981 (Box 42, Folder 225)
    - Program and Policy - Food Policy, 1982-1984, 1986 (Box 43, Folder 226)
    - Program and Policy - Food Policy - Reports - Pro FP-1 - 3, 3a,4, 1978-1979 (Box 43, Folder 227)
      Pro FP-1: Alex McCalla, Charles Mann, Christopher Mock; Food Policy Analysis in the Developing Countries, Draft Proposal of a Rockefeller Foundation Program; January 1979
      Pro FP-2: Schnittker Associates; Alternative Approaches to Ensuring Food Security in Developing Countries and Related Long-Term Research Needs; September 19, 1978
      Pro FP-3: Jo Ann Paulson; U.S. Food Agricultural Policy, The Domestic perspective; July 1978
      Pro FP-3a: Charles K. Mann; Field Notes on Food Policy; June 1-30, 1979
      Pro FP-4: John M. Underwood; Working Papers, Food Security and Food Policy in a World of Uncertainty; November 1979
    - Program and Policy - Food Policy - Reports - Pro FP-5, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 228)
      Pro FP-5: Betsy Bassan, Frances Clarity, Charles K. Mann, Julia McCartney; Information Retrieval and Exchange System for the Food and Agricultural Policy Collection (Poli-Col), Concept, Description, and User's Guide; 1980
    - Program and Policy - Food Policy - Reports - Pro FP-6, 1984 (Box 43, Folder 229)
      Pro FP-6: Food Policy at the Rockefeller Foundation; July 1984
    - Program and Policy - Food Policy - Reports - Pro FP-6a - Food and Agricultural Policy Documents 1-9, 1978-1979 (Box 43, Folder 230)
      Pro FP-6a: Food and Agricultural Policy Documents 1-9: Food Policy Task Force: Next Steps; Food and Agricultural Policy Analysis in the Developing Countries; Screening of Country Choices for Agricultural and Food Policy, Country Studies; Food and Agricultural Activities; Plans for the Investigation of Food and Agricultural Policy; Learning Activities and Basic Issues to be Addressed in the Development of Rockefeller Foundation-Supported Activities in this Area; Integrated Policy Analysis with Policymaking Process; Food and Agricultural Policy Activity Discussions in Turkey; 1978-1979
    - Program and Policy - Food Policy - Reports - Pro FP-6a - Food and Agricultural Policy Documents 10-15, 1979 (Box 43, Folder 231)
      Pro FP-6a: Food and Agricultural Policy Documents 10-15: Doc 10: Food and Agricultural Policy Activities: Turkey, May 22, 1979; Doc 11: Food and Agricultural Policy Activities: Turkey, May 30, 1979; Doc 12: Trip Report - Lebanon, Rome, Algeria and Tunisia Doc 13: Charles K. Mann; Field Notes on Food Policy; June 1-30, 1979 Doc 14: C. K. Mann; Food and Agricultural Policy Activities, East Africa, Need for Analytical Capacity in East Africa; Doc 15: C. K. Mann; Overseas Staffing for Rockefeller Foundation Food and Agricultural Policy Activities (draft) July 11
    - Program and Policy - Food Policy - Reports - Pro FP-6a - Food and Agricultural Policy Documents 17-18, 1979 (Box 43, Folder 232)
      Pro FP-6a: Food and Agricultural Policy Documents 17-18: Doc 17: Christopher Mock; Preliminar Description of Proposed Cereal Policiy Analysis in Tunisia; October 3, 1979 Doc. Christopher Mock; Description of Tunisia Cereal Policy Review; November 11, 1979
    - Program and Policy - Food Policy - Reports - Pro FP-6a - Food and Agricultural Policy Documents 19-20, 1979-1980 (Box 44, Folder 233)
      Pro FP-6a: Food and Agricultural Policy Documents 19-20: Food and Agricultural Policy; Food and Agricultural Policy Component; Food and Agricultural Policy - Kenya; Food Policy Seminar; Research Methodology; Aid Nutrition Program CKM Tunisian Trip Report; Food and Agricultural Policy - Chinese Model; Tunisia Field Trip; Food and Agricultural Policy Grant (Discussion); Identification of Policy Probelms in LDCs; Executive-Level Videotape Series; 1979-1980
    - Program and Policy - Food Policy - Reports - Pro FP-6a - Food and Agricultural Policy Documents 31-40, 1980 (Box 44, Folder 234)
      Pro FP-6a: Food and Agricultural Policy Documents 31-40: Address by Norman Borlaug at OSC; Reflections on the Oregon-Obrego-Mexico City Trip; Food and Agricultural Policy in Mexico; Food and Agricultural Policy; Notes; Information Retrieval and Exchange System for the Good and Agricultural Policy Collection (Poli-Coli); Proposed COH Consultant; Dr. David Dapice; Developing the Capacity of LDC Policy Makers (Malcom McPherson); The World Food Council's "Formulating a Food Sector Strategy"; 1980
    - Program and Policy - Food Policy - Reports - Pro FP-6a - Food and Agricultural Policy Documents 41-51, 1980 (Box 44, Folder 235)
      Pro FP-6a: Food and Agricultural Policy Documents 41-51: Comments on "Planning Technologies Appropriate to Farmers"; Concepts and Procedures; Working Hypothesis - Tunisia Cereal Study; A Note on Fundamental Principles; Plan of Work for Tunisia Cereal Policy Project; "Integrating Analytical Capacity with Decision-Making: The Case Method Approach"; Tunisia Food and Agricultural Policy Project; Criteria and Country Selection; 103 Food and Agricultural Policy Questions; 1980
    - Program and Policy - Food Policy - Reports - Pro FP-6a - Food and Agricultural Policy Documents 52-57, 1980 (Box 44, Folder 236)
      Pro FP-6a: Food and Agricultural Policy Documents 52-57: A Research and Training Program for Thailand; Current Status of the Tunisia Food and Agricultural Policy Project; Mexico Trip; Comments on Thailand; Summary Progress Report on Tunisia Cereal Policy Project; 1980
    - Program and Policy - Food Policy - Reports - Pro FP-6a - Food and Agricultural Policy Documents 58-69, 1980-1981 (Box 44, Folder 237)
      Pro FP-6a: Food and Agricultural Policy Documents 58-69: Interviews re: Kenya; Notes on Washington Trip; Results of Survey of COH Staff; Turkey; Current Status of the Rockefeller Foundation-Assisted Food and Agricultural Policy Activities; Kenya; Food and Agricultural Policy; Framework for the Design of a Kenyan/Rockefeller Foundation Food and Agricultural Policy; Livestock Development in Kenya: A Policy Statement; Turkey; Food and Nutrition Policy Project; Tunisia Cereal Policy Project - Christopher Mock's Report on Activities; Rockefeller Foundation COH-Food and Agricultural Policy; Tunisia Cereal Policy Project;1980-1981
    - Program and Policy - Food Policy - Reports - Pro FP-6a - Food and Agricultural Policy Documents 70-79, 1981 (Box 44, Folder 238)
      Pro FP-6a: Food and Agricultural Policy Documents 70-79: Ford Foundation Meeting on Food Subsidies; Project Review Visit - Ankara, Turkey; Summary of Mission Operational; Procedures and Conclusions; Kenya Food and Agricultural Policy Project (Charles Mann); Minnesota Trip Report; Tunisia Cereal Policy Project (Chistopher Mock); Food Policy in Tunisia; Tunisian Food and Agricultural Policy Project; Charles K. Mann Visit to Turkey, May 13-30, 1981; Trip Report; Chicago/Lansing; April 30-May2, 1981
    - Program and Policy - Food Policy - Reports - Pro FP-6a - Food and Agricultural Policy Documents 80-89, 1981-1982 (Box 45, Folder 239)
      Pro FP-6a: Food and Agricultural Policy Documents 80-89: COH-1982 Program Budget; Activities Report of Theodore Panayotou, A/D/C Food Policy and Resource Specialist; Food and Agricultural Policy Workshop and Field Report, Bangkok, Thailand (Charles Mann); Report on Rockefeller Foundation Internship 1979-1981 (Frances Clarity); Tunisian Food and Agricultural Policy Project - Field Evaluation; Agricultural Economics Society on Southeast Asia Meeting - Singapore; Should the Rockefeller Foundation Retain a Program in Food and Agriculture (Or is COH Program still needed?); COH Review; Report on Visiting Research Fellowship; Rockefeller Foundation Fellowships 1971-1980, a Statistical Overview of Three Programs; Conquest of Hunger, Education for Development, Population and Health (Mark Hibbs); 1981-1982
    - Program and Policy - Food Policy - Reports - Pro FP-6a - Food and Agricultural Policy Documents 90-96, 1981-1982 (Box 45, Folder 240)
      Pro FP-6a: Food and Agricultural Policy Documents 90-96: Report on the Meeting on Polish Agriculture (draft); COH Review Document; Women's Issues in COH Component IV; Trip Report on Turkey (David Dapice); Thailand Trip Report (David Dapice); Comments on August 1981 Thai Food Policy Workshop; Discussion Outline for Food Policy Working Group - International Institute for Applied Systems Analysis; Turkish Cereals Project Review and Food Policy Activities in Turkey; Agriculture on the Steep Slopes of Tropical America; Current Situation and Prospect for the Year 2000 (Joshua L. Posner, Malcom F. McPherson); 1981-1982
    - Program and Policy - Food Policy - Reports - Pro FP-6b-1 - Kenya, Chapters 1-11, 1979-1980 (Box 45, Folder 241)
      Pro FP-6b-1: Kenya Food and Agricultural Policy Project, Chapters 1-11; 1979-1980
    - Program and Policy - Food Policy - Reports - Pro FP-6b-1 - Kenya, Chapters 12-28, 1980-1981, 1983-1984 (Box 45, Folder 242)
      Pro FP-6b-1: Kenya Food and Agricultural Policy Project, Chapters 12-28; 1980-1981, 1983-1984
    - Program and Policy - Food Policy - Reports - Pro FP-6b-2 - Thailand, Chapters 1-14, 1978-1981 (Box 45, Folder 243)